<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>1 on Rohun Tripathi</title>
    <link>https://rohun-tripathi.github.io/publication_types/1/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 1 on Rohun Tripathi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 00:00:00 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://rohun-tripathi.github.io/publication_types/1/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Automatic Generation of Usable and Secure Audio reCAPTCHA</title>
      <link>https://rohun-tripathi.github.io/publication_chi/captcha/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rohun-tripathi.github.io/publication_chi/captcha/</guid>
      <description>Coming soon. Work under review.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Single View Height Prediction from satellite Imagery</title>
      <link>https://rohun-tripathi.github.io/publication/single-view/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rohun-tripathi.github.io/publication/single-view/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Semantic Segmentation with Scarce Data</title>
      <link>https://rohun-tripathi.github.io/publication/semantic-seg/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2018 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rohun-tripathi.github.io/publication/semantic-seg/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Enterprise Scale Privacy Aware Occupancy Sensing</title>
      <link>https://rohun-tripathi.github.io/publication_chi/occupancy-sensing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rohun-tripathi.github.io/publication_chi/occupancy-sensing/</guid>
      <description>Abstract. Location based services inside smart buildings are dependent on scalable localization methods. However, for enterprises, privacy of individual employees is a major concern. In this paper, we present a privacy aware occupancy sensing mechanism for large scale enterprises with multiple floors in multiple buildings of multiple cities. This is achieved through Wi-Fi fingerprint based localization methods implemented on edge devices. We present some preliminary results on occupancy sensing from our pilot study inside the office spaces of IBM India.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RNNs based Indic word-wise script identification using character-wise training</title>
      <link>https://rohun-tripathi.github.io/publication/indic-script/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2017 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rohun-tripathi.github.io/publication/indic-script/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Path Planning in Ellipsoidal Configuration Space using Silhouette method</title>
      <link>https://rohun-tripathi.github.io/publication_robotics/silhouette/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rohun-tripathi.github.io/publication_robotics/silhouette/</guid>
      <description>Abstract. This work presents the methodology used for implementing Silhouette method for Robot motion planning in Configuration spaces in arbitrary dimensions. A collection of ellipsoids are used to design and implement this Configuration Space of the robot. The path is then designed based on the Silhouette method as described by Canny [2], which creates semi-free paths in the configuration space and is complete. Djikstra’s algorithm is used to connect the paths obtained.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Programming by Demonstration and Dynamical Systems for Robot Learning</title>
      <link>https://rohun-tripathi.github.io/publication_robotics/lfd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2014 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rohun-tripathi.github.io/publication_robotics/lfd/</guid>
      <description>Abstract. This work presents the methodology used for implementing programming by demonstration methods on a Universal Robot UR10. We used non-linear time-invariant Dynamical Systems that can imitate unconventional forms of motion. Gaussian Mixture Models were used to model input data and parameters of DS were optimized based on MSE and Log-likelihood cost functions. We incorporated a Kinect to detect users and ensure safety. Our system learns any non-circular path within three manual demonstrations and was spatially asymptotically stable.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>